udonzone.com 2016-03-16

# Privacy Policy | UdonZONE

At UdonZONE – DIY, Home Design & Interior, we respect your privacy and are committed to protecting personal information you may provide us through our Website.

This Privacy Policy explains what information may be collected on Architecture & Interior Design, how we use this information, and under what circumstances we may disclose the information to third parties.

### The Information We Collect and How We Use It

Our Website typically collects two types of information about you:

Information that you provide that personally identifies you

If you send us an e-mail or a comment, you may choose to provide us with personal information, such as your name or your e-mail address. We use the information to improve our service to you, provide you with updates, or to respond to your requests.

Whether or not you provide this information is your choice; however, in many instances this type of information is required to participate in the particular activity, realize a benefit we may offer, or gain access to certain content on our Website.

Information that does not personally identify you, that we automatically collect when you visit our Website

If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will gather and store certain information about your visit automatically. This information does not identify you personally. We typically collect and store details about your visit, such as the Internet domain (for example, â€œwebsite.comâ€? if you use a private Internet access account), your IP address address (an IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer whenever you are surfing the Web), the type of browser and operating system used to access our site, the pages you visit, the date and time you access our Website and if you linked to our website from another website, the address of that website.

We use the information we collect to count the number and type of visitors to the different pages on our site, and to help us make our site more useful to visitors like you.

### Keeping Your Information Secure

We have implemented security measures we consider reasonable and appropriate to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. Please be advised, however, that while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information and privacy, we cannot guarantee or warrant the security of any information you disclose or transmit to us online and are not responsible for the theft, destruction, or inadvertent disclosure of your personally identifiable information. From time to time we evaluate new technology for protecting information, and when appropriate, we upgrade our information security systems.

**Cookies**

To save you comment’s information every time you visit Architecture & Design, we place a little text file called a â€œcookieâ€? on your hard drive. It sits in your web browser directory.

A cookie lets us store your profile information on your computer and lets our website retrieve it when you visit our site. No other website can use or view the cookie set by Architecture & Design.

Cookies help us create a speedy web experience by remembering your address and email information, so you don’t have to re-type it when making comments.

We may use cookies on the website for the purpose of monitoring your and other users’ activity in order to improve the website and the services available to you. If you don’t want us to use cookies when you use our website, you will need to change your Internet browser settings so that your browser does not accept them.

### Links to Other sites

Architecture & Design has links to partners and other sites. When you link to another site, you are no longer on our site and are subject to the privacy policy of the new website.

### Restriction of Liability

Architecture & Design makes no claims, promises or guarantees about the accuracy, completeness, or adequacy of the contents of this website and expressly disclaims liability for errors and omissions in the contents of this website.

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may change some of the statements in this Privacy Policy at any time. We will prominently post notice of the changes at this URL. Any material changes to this Privacy Policy will be effective when posted.

Your continued use of this site following the posting of any amendment, modification or change shall constitute your acceptance thereof.
